genuitec.com 2019-06-04

# Website Privacy Policy - Genuitec

### INTRODUCTION

Genuitec LLC (referred to as “Genuitec”, “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice) respects your privacy and takes your right to privacy seriously. This privacy policy (“Policy”) deals with personally-identifiable information that may be collected from you, through our interactions with you and through our products. As used in this Privacy Statement, “personal data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’). An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

By using Genuitec LLC site or products, you signify your agreement to the Privacy Policy and [Terms of Use](https://www.genuitec.com/products/legal/). You are not required to provide personal data to Genuitec. However, if you choose not to provide your personal data, we may not be able to provide you with our products or services or all of their functionalities or to respond to your inquiries. We may give you additional privacy information that is specific to a product or service in Supplements to this Policy and other notices you may see while using our products or services. If there is a difference between such notices and this Policy, the notices should be considered first.

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these terms at any time. Please check periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site and available products following the posting of changes to these terms will signify your acceptance of the revised terms. They were last updated on May 25, 2018.

This Privacy Policy and our obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”) to data subjects residing in the European Union will supersede any inconsistent terms in the Terms of Use.

### SCOPE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY

The Privacy Policy applies to all information you provide through this Site or products available through this Site. If you have submitted information to any third parties through our Site or products, as provided below, the privacy policies of those third parties will govern how your data will be used. Please check the privacy policies of any third party we link to before providing it with your personal information.

### COLLECTION OF DATA

We collect two general types of information from users: personal data; and aggregated data.

### PERSONAL DATA

Genuitec collects personal information directly from you when you interact with us through our websites, products and services including, without limitation, when you:

Create an account through our websites (individual or corporate);  
Make online purchases or register products;  
Request support;  
Register for a webcast or other event;  
Request information or materials;  
Participate in surveys or evaluations;  
Participate in promotions, contests, or giveaways;  
Apply for employment;  
Submit questions or comments; or  
Submit content or posts on our customer portal pages or other interactive webpages.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, the types of personal data collected directly from you may include, without limitation:

Information used to communicate with you, such as name, title, company name, email address, telephone number, postal address and language;  
Information that Genuitec maintains in association with your account, such as your username, password, payment information, purchase records, credit and billing status and support inquiries; and  
Information contained in your job inquiries or applications, such as resume, cover letter, age, education, professional history and contact details.

### AGGREGATE AND PRODUCT USAGE INFORMATION

Aggregated information, such as which page users access and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registration information, is collected through various methods. In the course of using our site, we also automatically track certain information about your browser interactions. This information includes the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from Us, Our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable unless related to the management of your subscription account. So although your browsing session will be logged, we will not log any personally identifiable information of your browsing. You can also opt out of Google Analytics opt out using [this tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Product usage information is collected as part of your ongoing use of the products Genuitec provides in our attempt to better serve users and customize user experience. Such information include feature use patterns to determine feature popularity in order to dedicate necessary resources and development priorities. Product usage information is anonymized to remove any personal data connection to the usage metrics resulting in raw metrics data that cannot be tied to personally identifiable information at time of collection and on our servers.

You provide some of the data we collect directly, and we get some of it by collecting data about your interactions and use with our products. You have the right to decline to provide any personal information. Many of our products require some personal data to provide access to our products or services. If you choose not to provide data necessary to provide you with a product or feature, you cannot use that product or feature. Likewise, where we need to collect personal data by law or to enter into or carry out a contract with you, and you do not provide the data, we will not be able to enter into the contract; or if this relates to an existing product you’re using, we may have to suspend or cancel it.

### COOKIES

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. Details for our Cookies policy is available here.

### USE OF DATA

We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties without your written permission. The extent of disclosure is limited to the following:

International transfers of personal data: Our products and services may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world. Therefore, your personal data may be transferred across international borders outside the country where you use our services, including to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA) that do not have laws providing specific protection for personal data or that have different legal rules on data protection. In such cases we use measures to provide adequate protection for your personal data as required by applicable law

Mandatory disclosures: We may be obligated by mandatory law to disclose your personal data to certain authorities or other third parties, for example, to law enforcement agencies in the countries where we or third parties acting on our behalf operate. We may also disclose and otherwise process your personal data in accordance with applicable law to defend Genuitec legitimate interests, for example, in civil or criminal legal proceedings.

Mergers and Acquisitions: If we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize our businesses in certain countries, this may involve us disclosing personal data to prospective or actual purchasers and their advisers, or receiving personal data from sellers and their advisers.

### DATA RETENTION

We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

### MINORS

We do not knowingly collect information from children and we do not target the Services to children. If you believe a child under 13 (in the United States) or 16 (in the EEA) has submitted personal information to us, please contact us at admin@genuitec.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our files.

### EDITING OR DELETING YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION

You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting [your user account control panel](https://www.genuitec.com/member-home/). You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact [the site administrator](mailto:%20admin@genuitec.com). Content or other data that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as articles published, may continue to remain on the site at the site editor’s discretion, even after your user account is deleted. Please see the site’s [Terms of Use](https://www.genuitec.com/products/legal/) for more information.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact the [site administrator](mailto:%20admin@genuitec.com).

### COOKIES AND HOW WE USE THEM

This policy details how Genuitec LLC uses cookies and cookie-like files and technologies on its websites, e.g. Local Shared Objects, also known as “Flash cookies”, web beacons, etc. We refer to these generically as “cookies”. If you visit our websites and your browser settings accept cookies, we consider this as acceptance of our use of cookies.

#### What are cookies and how do they work?

Cookies are small files that are sent to and stored in your computer by the websites you visit. Cookies are stored in your browser’s file directory. Next time you visit the site, your browser will read the cookie and relay the information back to the website or element that originally set the cookie. To learn more about these technologies and how they work, please see e.g. allaboutcookies.org.

#### Why does Genuitec use cookies?

At Genuitec domains, we use cookies to offer you a smoother experience. View your options for managing cookies below.

#### Basic functions

These cookies are essential for running our websites and are the key to providing you a seamless experience. You can navigate uninterrupted e.g. by remembering language and country choices you’ve made and by preserving authentication to secure parts of the domain. These cookies also remember products of interest when you are redirected to an Operator site for a possible purchase.

#### Site improvement

These cookies enable us to improve our websites by looking at how they are used. We do analytical profiling to understand e.g. unique users reading a particular article (to know what is popular) or if a video file was viewed or abandoned half way through. We also look at where content is accessed so we know how to arrange our sites for optimal user experience. We count clicks on “Like” and “Tweet” plugins and what content from our sites was shared or referenced.

#### Advertising

We use these cookies to dynamically serve Genuitec ads on both Genuitec and selected third party websites.

Our domains may also include elements that set cookies on behalf of a third party, e.g. a “Like”-button from Facebook or a “Tweet”-button from Twitter.

#### How can I manage cookies?

You can review the options available to manage cookies in your browser. The browser can be used to manage cookies relating to basic functions, site improvement, personalization and advertising. Different browsers use different ways to disable cookies, but they are usually found under a Tools or Options menu. You can also consult the browser’s help menu. In addition to cookie management, browsers usually let you control files similar to cookies, such as Local Shared Objects, e.g. by enabling the browser’s privacy mode. Genuitec uses third party vendor managed advertising cookies to promote its products in both Genuitec and non-Genuitec web sites. You may be able to opt-out from certain third party managed advertising cookies through third party cookie management sites.

Disabling cookies may prevent you from using certain parts of Genuitec websites. If you delete your cookies from the browser, you may need to remember to re-install opt-out cookies.

#### How long do we keep the information?

It depends based on the type of cookies. Session cookies expire when you close the browser. Persistent cookies, including Local Shared Objects (“Flash cookies”), have typical expiration dates ranging from two months up to a couple of years.

#### What else should you know?

Genuitec may from time to time change this Policy. However, if this Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, Genuitec will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this Policy and on this site’s home page. We recommend that you revisit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy.

If you have additional questions, please contact us by writing to:

Genuitec LLC  
2221 Justin Road #119-340  
Flower Mound, TX 75028
